<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jim Dücker</title>
    <link>https://jimducker.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jim Dücker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jimducker.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://jimducker.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimducker.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? I&amp;rsquo;m a 19 year old software developer student currently living in The Netherlands, but looking to go to Sweden for my next internship. I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a passion for all kinds of stuff regarding technology, but I especially love to build software.
What I do I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying software development for around 3 years at the Koning Willem I College in &amp;rsquo;s-Hertogenbosch, and interned at Heras. Though I learn a lot at school, my interest takes me even further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://jimducker.nl/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimducker.nl/experience/</guid>
      <description>Heras During the first half of my second year I interned at Heras. Heras is an international protection company. That means that they come up with and create solutions across many different sectors. They&amp;rsquo;re widely known for their security solutions which include fences, gates, cameras and other solutions.
I interned as a software developer along with two other interns for six months. During our internship we were tasked with building a full-stack application that would be used by prisons in the Netherlands and the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://jimducker.nl/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimducker.nl/skills/</guid>
      <description>During my studies I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired a diverse set of skills, both from school and on my own. Below you will find more thorough explanations of how much I know and why I think it&amp;rsquo;s a good skill to have. Shortly summed up this is what I currently know:
Linux HTML / CSS JavaScript HUGO PHP SQL C# / .NET Xamarin DevOps Git VMware Linux Linux has been one of my hobbies for about a year now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
